the city of Polson recently adopt an
official no smoking policy in its city
parks the Polson City Commission
approved the ban on tobacco use in all
parks owned by the city back on May 18th
and the signs are already up at multiple
parks across town the Parks and
Recreation Department says as more
people turn to public outdoor recreation
areas during the pandemic it is the
perfect time to increase safety measures
director Paton Allen adds the measure
will protect young people secondhand
smokes not good for all of our parks
that are kid-friendly sporting events
those are the areas that we targeted
demand to protect them from secondhand
smoke now Len says the department hopes
the signs are enough to enforce the ban
but if you get caught the first citation
will be a verbal warning